everybody what is going on welcome to
大家欢迎 来到
the 11th Cavey basics tutorial video in
在 11 凯维基础知识视频教程
this video we're gonna be talking about
这个视频我们要去谈论
adding our I don't know drawing
添加我们 不知道绘图
application to this little application
应用于这个小应用
here and using the buttons to go back
这里并使用按钮返回
and forth between the application and
和之间的应用程序和
say the home screen or whatever you
说主屏幕 或 任何你
could envision it being a game or I
可以设想它是一个游戏或我
don't know stock prices or what pretty
不知道股票价格还是什么漂亮的
much whatever you wanted so this is what
无论你想要什么，所以这是什么
we left off with and now basically this
我们离开了，现在 基本上是这样
will be our this will be our home screen
将是我们的这 将是我们的主 屏幕
and then we'll rename next screen to be
然后我们将重命名下一个屏幕
I don't know draw okay
我 不 知道画好
so let's close out of this and go ahead
让我们关闭的这一点，并继续
and get started so this is actually
并开始， 所以这实际上是
going to be fairly simplistic I've now
我现在已经相当简单了
I'm using main to main to cavies I'm
我使用主要以 主 让豚鼠我
gonna change this the loader to main to
要把这个装载机改成主要
now KB uh and that should be the only
现在KB 呃那应该是唯一的
thing to change and anyway moving on so
事情改变和 移动 反正 就这么
how do we actually make these changes
我们如何实际做出这些 改变
and move forward so first we're going to
并继续前进， 所以我们首先要做的
need our actual drawing applications so
需要我们的实际绘图 应用程序
I'm just gonna rewrite it it's a pretty
我只是要重写它而已
quick right anyways so we had a class it
无论如何快速正确，所以我们有一个类
was we'll call that we call it painter I
我们会打电话 给我们，叫我画家
guess or I think we called it draw or
猜测或我认为我们称之为绘制或
something before and it actually needs
实际上需要的东西
to inherit from widget which we haven't
从 我们没有的小部件 继承
imported so let's actually make our
进口，所以让我们实际上使我们的
theme necessary imports as well so first
主题必要的进口以及 首先
we want to have from TV UI x dot widget
我们希望从电视界面的x点小部件
we're going to import widget then we
我们将导入小部件， 然后我们
need we're also going to need line and
需要我们也需要线和
we'll be using buttons and we'll really
我们将使用按钮， 我们会真的
use the button in here most likely I
使用按钮，在这里最有可能的 我
think we'll get a way out without
认为我们会 在没有的情况下 找到 出路
importing button so then from k V dot
然后从K V点导入按钮
graphics import line X let's capital L
图形输入线X让我们大写L
line okay so now we're ready to continue
行好，所以现在我们准备继续
on with our painter inheriting from
与我们的画家 继承
widget and now we're going to define the
窗口小部件，现在我们要 定义
on touch down so again ask yourself
在接触时再次 问自己
where does on touch down actually come
实际接触的地方在哪里
from is that our code or their code next
由是 ，我们的代码或他们的代码下一个
self touch again is that like my code or
自我再次触摸就像我的代码或
is that their code
是他们的代码
then we're going to say with self dot
那么我们会用自己的点来说
canvas more is that my coder they're
画布更多的是 我的编码器
good touch UT and then the element here
很好的触摸UT，然后在这里的元素
that we want is line equals capital line
我们想要的是线等于资本线
and then the points are equal to touch X
然后点数等于触摸X
and touch whoops
并触摸哎呀
touch dot y and uh if this feels like
触摸点和呃，如果这感觉
it's going too fast for you go back like
你的回头速度太快了
three tutorials I think is where we
三个教程我认为是我们的地方
actually built this originally so you
实际上建立了这个原本所以 你
can go back there and see how that how
可以回到那里， 看看 如何
it was done if you want more explanation
它是如果你想要更多的解释完成
there then again we have on defined on
那么我们又有了 定义
underscore touch underscore move self
下划线触摸下划线移动自己
dot ourself comma touch and touch UD
点自己的 逗号触摸和 触摸UD
line dot points plus equals and touch
线点点加等于和触摸
XCOM on touch why okay and that's
触摸XCOM为什么 好，那 就是了
basically it we're not gonna write
基本上它 不是 让你 去 写
anything else here this should all be
这里所有的东西都应该是这样
acceptable so this is our little widget
可以接受， 所以这是我们的小部件
right same widget that we had before and
我们收到了同样的权利和窗口小部件
now what we want to do is add this
现在我们想要做的就是添加这个
widget to our kind of screen changing
小部件来改变我们的屏幕
that we've already got so we want this
我们已经 有了，所以我们想要这个
widget painter in another screen but we
小工画家在另一个屏幕上，但我们
actually don't have to do that via this
实际上不需要 通过这个来做到这一点
file we're going to do it via the key V
文件我们将 通过关键字V来完成
file so in another screen we'll get rid
文件在另一个屏幕中， 我们将摆脱
of button for now we'll eventually have
现在我们 终将拥有按钮
a but in there just to it but for now
但在那里只是为了它， 但现在
we're not gonna have anything we're just
我们 不会有任何我们只是
going to say name other and then we add
去 说其他名字然后我们添加
our fun painter class here so we should
我们这里有趣的画家课，所以我们应该
just be able to say just painter nothing
只能 说画家什么都没有
more so it would be as if we were
更像是我们一样
actually adding the painter into another
实际上将 画家 添加 到另一个画家
screen down here but we're not really
在这里屏幕， 但我们不是真的
but anyway so it's a painter widget and
但无论如何， 所以这是一个画家小部件和
we're adding it to another screen so
我们将它添加到另一个 屏幕
let's save that and run this and
让我们保存并运行这个和
hopefully this works out so we go to the
希望这能解决，所以我们去 了
next screen and sure enough we are able
下一个屏幕， 并确信 我们 能够
to
至
draw yay ok so that's how we were able
画耶 确定，所以这就是我们如何能够
to add just a simple little widget that
添加一个简单的 小部件
we had built initially that widget was
我们最初构建了这个 小部件
just heading straight into this page but
只是直接进入这个页面，但
this one obviously has sort of multiple
这个显然 有多重
pages but now you might wonder ok at
但现在你可能想知道 在 哪里
what if we want to get back to the main
如果我们想回到主体，该怎么办？
page like what if this was like a
如果这就像一个网页一样
settings page and you wanted the user to
设置页面，你希望用户
be able to get back to the main page you
能够回到 你的 主页面
need to have another button on here so I
需要在这里有另一个按钮，所以我
think that's what we'll do in the next
认为这就是我们将在下一节做
video we'll add a button to go kind of
视频中，我们将添加一个按钮 来实现
back and forth kind of like we did
像我们 一样 前后来回
before only the button took up the whole
之前只有 按钮占据了整体
page and in fact there will be no new
页面，实际上 不会有新的
code in the next videos for us adding a
在下一个视频中为我们添加一个代码
button is concerned I encourage you to
按钮有关 我鼓励你
go ahead and try to see if you can add a
继续尝试 看看你是否可以添加一个
button just a small button I think we'll
按钮只是 一个小按钮， 我想我们会的
probably put ours up and maybe in the
可能会把我们的，也许在我们的
top here to go back home but just try to
顶部这里回家 ，但只是 尝试
add your own small button and see if you
添加你自己的小按钮，看看你是否
can and if you can't then obviously you
可以， 如果你不能 那么显然你
can still check the next video so
仍然可以检查下一个视频
anyways that's what we'll do in the next
无论如何，这 就是我们接下来要做的
video so stay tuned for that if you guys
视频， 敬请关注 ，如果你们
have any questions or comments please
请有任何问题或意见
feel free to leave them below otherwise
随意将 它们 留 在下面
as always thanks for watching thanks for
一如既往感谢收看感谢
all the support in the subscriptions
订阅中的所有支持
until next time
直到下一次